{
    "subject": "Maurice_Cloche",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "La_Portatrice_di_pane__1950_film_",
    "human_readable": "Maurice Cloche directed the film La Portatrice di pane (1950).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9420545101165771,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Maurice Cloche."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9204596281051636,
            "question": "Who directed the film La Portatrice di pane?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8740726709365845,
            "question": "Is Maurice Cloche known for directing films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8602287769317627,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by Maurice Cloche?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7792201042175293,
            "question": "What year was the film La Portatrice di pane released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.722037136554718,
            "question": "In what year was La Portatrice di pane made?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7200546860694885,
            "question": "Are there any other films directed by Maurice Cloche?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6726177930831909,
            "question": "What genre is the film La Portatrice di pane?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5200066566467285,
            "question": "What is the subject matter of La Portatrice di pane?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3906727433204651,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Maurice Cloche?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Maurice Cloche directed the film La Portatrice di pane (1950).",
            "html": "yago_14635_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the subject matter of La Portatrice di pane?",
            "html": "yago_14635_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film La Portatrice di pane?",
            "html": "yago_14635_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other films directed by Maurice Cloche?",
            "html": "yago_14635_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14635_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14635_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14635_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14635_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14635_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14635_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14635_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14635_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14635_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14635_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The query is \"Maurice Cloche directed the film La Portatrice di pane (1950).\" and the answer should be either \"yes\" or \"no\".\n\nAfter analyzing the documents, I found that:\n\n* In file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_14635/re-ranker-msmarco/104.txt, it is mentioned that Maurice Cloche directed the film LA PORTATRICE DI PANE - 1950.\n* The title of the film \"La Portatrice di pane\" (1950) is also confirmed in file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_14635/re-ranker-msmarco/104.txt.\n\nTherefore, based on the documents, the answer is:\n\n{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Maurice Cloche was a French filmmaker and director, and there is information about his film \"La Portatrice di pane\" (The Bread Peddler) from 1950. This supports the statement that Maurice Cloche directed the film \"La Portatrice di pane.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}